let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "What is a style sheet? ",
        answer: "A. css",
        options: [
            "A. css",
            "B. lay out settings",
            "C. template",  
            "D. font and size documents",  
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "What is URL?", 
        answer: "A. reference", 
        options: [
            "A. reference",
            "B. link", 
            "C. location",
            "D. source"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "What is URL stand for?",
        answer: "C. Uniforme Resource Locator",
        options: [
            "A. Ultra Registered Link", 
            "B. Unifide Reliable Link", 
            "C. Uniforme Resource Locator", 
            "D. Universal Resource Link" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "What is the use of imported css?",
        answer: "D. @import rule allows you to import a stylesheet into another stylesheet",
        options: [
            "A. @import rule allows you to save the documents",
            "B. @import rule allows you to go to other applications",
            "C. @import rule allows you to import an image in stylesheet",
            "D. @import rule allows you to import a stylesheet into another stylesheet"

        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "The value of style attribute is a combination of style declarations separated by?",
        answer: "A. semicolon",
        options: [
            "A. semicolon", 
            "B. comma", 
            "C. exclamation mark", 
            "D. parenthesis" 

        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "You can use style attribute of any HTML element to define what? ",
        answer: "B. Style rules",
        options: [
            "A. Inline", 
            "B. Style rules", 
            "C. attributes value", 
            "D. attributes element", 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "How to edit font-weight using css? ",
        answer: "C. use the font-weight property",
        options: [
            "A. locate the text where you want to change the font", 
            "B. use the font-stretch property", 
            "C. use the font-weight property", 
            "D. use the < b > element" 

        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "What is syntax in html? ",
        answer: "A. the order in which elements appear or are written",
        options: [
            "A. the order in which elements appear or are written",
            "B. the arrangement of words",
            "C. a set of rules",
            "D. a set of syntax language"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "What is html element?",
        answer: "B. a component of an html",
        options: [
            "A. a part of abstract",
            "B. a component of an html",
            "C. a basic part of a whole",
            "D. a smaller component of a larger system"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "What href? ",
        answer: "D. specifies the url of the page",
        options: [
            "A. a link", 
            "B. an href link tag", 
            "C. a reference", 
            "D. specifies the url of the page"            

        ]
    },
]
Enter
